sdsc.edu 2014-05-26

# San Diego Supercomputer Center: Privacy

The San Diego Supercomputer Center (SDSC) is committed to your privacy within the applicable laws of the State of California and the Policies of the University of California. This disclosure includes:

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours is collected from you through the website
  2. The organization collecting the information
  3. How the information is used
  4. With whom the information may be shared
  5. The choices available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under SDSC control
  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information

Please contact SDSC at [communications@sdsc.edu](mailto:communications@sdsc.edu) if you feel we're not abiding by our posted privacy notice.

### Information Collection and Use

SDSC is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. SDSC collects information from our users at several different points on our website. The information is used exclusively to deliver information and services to you.

### Subscription Services

SDSC offers publications through both physical (mail) and electronic (e-mail and Web) distribution methods. If a user wishes to subscribe to our e-mail newsletter, printed science magazine, RSS feed service, or other printed or digital publication we ask for contact information such as name and e-mail address through an online or mailed registration form.

### Log Files

We use Web log files to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' use of our site, and gather broad demographic information for usability studies. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that SDSC is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by SDSC.

### Security

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the site, that information is protected both online and off-line.

### Correcting/Updating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as e-mail address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us.

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
